#### Contact

dmtrshatokhin@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/dmtrshat (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
REST APIs
Unit Testing
Test Automation

# Dmitrii Shatokhin

Front End Architect @ Support Partners | Software Engineer, Opensource enthusiast

Warsaw, Mazowieckie, Poland

## Summary

Hi there!

I'm Dmitrii, a versatile software engineer and architect with over a decade of experience. My journey in tech started with C, C++, and Python, and has evolved to encompass web development, AI, and data science. Inspired by Robert Heinlein's quote, "Specialization is for insects," I love exploring diverse technologies and solving complex problems.

When I'm not coding, I cherish time with my family, creating music, and dreaming about space adventures. Feel free to connect if you want to chat about tech, science, or just share a laugh. Cheers!

## Experience

Support Partners
Front End Architect
January 2022 - Present (2 years 7 months)
Warsaw, Mazowieckie, Poland

As a Front End Architect, I play a key role in planning and developing product roadmaps, actively participating in defining and implementing the project architecture (but I also sometimes develop the backend part). I personally handle the selection of technologies and the writing of critical code, as well as dividing overall tasks into subtasks and coordinating developer activities. I contribute significantly to the development, often taking on the most complex tasks, and provide technical leadership and mentorship in the team. Additionally, I am involved in writing and updating technical documentation, ensuring clear understanding and adherence to design decisions.

Graph
Senior Frontend Developer
January 2021 - January 2022 (1 year 1 month)
St Petersburg, St Petersburg City, Russia

I was engaged in frontend development for various projects and systems. I improved and optimized existing projects by proposing new solutions. Additionally, I was involved in mentoring.

#### GeekBrains

Teacher of the course "Python Developer"

November 2017 - December 2020 (3 years 2 months)

#### actiTIME

Senior Frontend Engineer August 2020 - November 2020 (4 months) St Petersburg City, Russia

I was involved in the development of the company's main product - Time Tracking Software. This included its improvement and the transition to a new version with a new interface and new technologies.

#### **SBNT**

Lead Software Engineer December 2019 - March 2020 (4 months) Munich, Bavaria, Germany

Med-startup (due to COVID-19 it was frozen)

#### G2

Senior Frontend Developer August 2019 - November 2019 (4 months) Magnitogorsk, Chelyabinsk, Russia

Advance Engeneering Software Engineer September 2018 - July 2019 (11 months) Yekaterinburg, Sverdlovsk, Russia

Uber

Software Engineer
May 2018 - September 2018 (5 months)
Lidar startup (for self-driving cars)

Mail.ru Group Software Engineer April 2017 - January 2018 (10 months) MMK

Software Engineer

November 2014 - November 2017 (3 years 1 month)

Magnitogorsk, Chelyabinsk, Russia

Automation of production processes

Магнитогорский Государственный Технический Университет (МГТУ) им. Г.И. Носова (МГТУ)
Full Stack Developer
September 2016 - May 2017 (9 months)
Magnitogorsk, Chelyabinsk, Russia

Work on the educational portal of the university. Part time

Freelance | Self-Employed Full Stack Developer January 2014 - May 2017 (3 years 5 months) Magnitogorsk, Chelyabinsk, Russia

Freelance

Project work in several Canadian web studios

### Education

Магнитогорский Государственный Технический Университет (МГТУ) им. Г.И. Носова (МГТУ)

Bachelor's degree, Архитектура · (2016 - 2018)